[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
I caught him.
But a bunch of people came.
They shot at me.
That's why they got him!
We went up against big people.
And they look like
an organized syndicate.
If that lawyer screws up,
I know another way.
The woman who caught Victor
is General Ricardo Jacinto's
daughter.
You sure you know
who you're messing with?
Are you sure about
your investigation?
We did our homework.
Our op was completely legit.
Are we still doing
everything wrong?
Dad sees things
we don't, Sam.
We're still new to the force.
He's the former chief.
My team and I caught
a major criminal.
You forgot your stubbornness
destroyed this family!
[LIQUID POURING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Have you talked to Ricardo yet?
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
He said he'd see
what he can do.
And if that doesn't work?
He can't say no to me.
He might've played me before,
but not anymore.
I have more money now,
and way more power.
And it's all because of you
and our businesses.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[GLASS CLINKS]
We built this together.
We'll work to make it bigger.
Mm-hmm.
Lucas and Victor will carry
on what we started.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES,
THEN FADES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
[WHISPERS] Mom.
Still awake?
[SIGHS SOFTLY]
It's just hard to sleep
after everything.
Yeah.
I am so proud of you.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you, Mommy.
You're always there for me.
Thank you for being
so understanding.
I know I messed up
with our family.
I try to make up for it
every single day.
I keep trying to prove...
...I'm a good daughter.
I'm not perfect,
but I did my best.
You don't have
to prove anything.
Not to me...
or to anyone else.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh... But I do to Dad.
I know...
I still need to earn
his love and forgiveness.
If that day comes,
I'm willing to wait.
I deserve this punishment.
No.
You know what you deserve?
You deserve
unconditional love.
Your daddy may not be
giving you that right now,
but you deserve nothing less
than that.
That's kind of hard
to believe in.
That I'm worthy of love.
Don't say that.
Don't think like that.
What is the meaning
of being human?
It's to love.
Don't deprive yourself of it.
[SOBS]
I love you.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SAM SOBBING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Django.
Here's the money I earned.
Is this all?
I thought you had
a great catch?
That's all inside his wallet.
What's the big idea?!
- Nothing?
- I told you, there's nothing!
[NECKLACE JINGLING]
[CHAIR THUDS]
What's this?
That's mine.
My girlfriend gave that to me.
What a sweet girlfriend
you have there.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS IN PAIN]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING IN PAIN]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
You know that I take down
everyone who messes with me.
Please, Django...
But I won't do that to you.
Because you did get in
a lot of money after all.
So I'll spare you this time.
But don't ever show yourself
to me again.
Do you understand?!
- Yes, Django.
- [BLOW LANDS]
[THUDDING]
Get him out of my face.
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING IN PAIN]
Get him out!
I'll get you some day, Django.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BINOY] I thought we were going
to strike it big.
It's so hard to catch Mr. Chan.
[TEKLA] Shut up! Stop whining.
It's not like Gabo wished
to let Tiger get away.
[DABOY] Please, Gabo,
just give us something!
[IPE] You're really not going
to stop, aren't you?
Want me to beat you up?
[TOLITS] I know that guy.
He's one of Django's guys, Ben.
Gabo.
I'm Ben.
I have something to tell you.
Why?
What do you need from Gabo?
Gabo,
my guilt has been eating me up
this past few days.
I know who shot your father,
Sir Rudy.
[BLADE WHOOSHING]
- Gabo!
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Who shot my father?
Who was it?!
It's Django, Gabo.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I saw it.
We were together back then.
During the riot
at the demolition.
If you're messing with me,
I'll slit your throat open.
Understand?
- Huh?!
- Gabo!
[THUDDING]
Gabo.
Gabo, what now?
Django will pay for what
he did to my father.
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
- Gabo!
- Come on!
[LAUGHING] That bastard Ben
thought he could get past me.
- [THUDDING]
- [GABO] Go ahead!
Just try and break free!
[INAUDIBLE]
[BONG] Go ahead and try!
Try me!
[BONG] Nobody move!
You bastard.
So you're the one
who shot my father.
- Huh?!
- [PAQUITO] Gabo!
Ho-- hold on!
What are you talking about?
It's this son of yours!
He shot my father!
And now he's at the hospital
fighting for his life!
Gabo, it wasn't me
who shot Sir Rudy!
Don't even try to fool me,
you bastard.
Someone already spilled it!
You know me, Gabo!
If I'll get back at you,
I'll do it to you directly!
I won't waste any time
on your father!
A cop shot your father, Gabo!
And everyone knows it!
Gabo, let's talk this out!
Your accusation is not true!
You know us!
If we were the ones
who shot Rudy,
he would've been
lying in a casket by now!
Who told you that anyway?!
Ack!
Ben did!
Huh?
I already fired him!
Bastard stole from me!
He just wanted
to get back at me!
Gabo.
Maybe what Django's saying
is true.
[BONG] This is hard, Gabo.
We're unsure about it.
That Ben guy just came
out of the blue either.
Gabo, believe me.
That bastard just wants
to see us fight!
[TEKLA] Gabo, let's go already!
Django is a jerk
but he's got a point!
If he wanted to get back at you,
he'll do it to you directly!
- [GABO BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Ack!
If I find out...
that you were indeed the one
who shot my father...
I'll pick up where I left off.
[THUDDING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BONG] Stay back!
Stay back.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Let's go.
- Quick!
Let's move!
[GRUNTS]
You're really something.
You made Django and Gabo
fight each other.
Well, doing that helped me
get back at Django.
I hope they both die.
[LAUGHTER]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THUD]
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You lied to me!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
You bastard!
Who shot my father?!
It was Django.
He was the one
who shot your father.
Stop lying, you bastard!
Django himself said that he
didn't shoot Mister Rudy.
Damn you!
You told Gabo that Django
shot Mister Rudy
because Django's group
beat you up
for stealing money
from them.
That's how he plays, Gabo.
He has always been like that.
He can't be trusted
with money.
He lied to you so that
you and Django will fight
while he gets his revenge.
- You bastard!
- Ah!
How dare you put
Gabo in trouble!
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANS]
- [KICK LANDS]
[IPE] You deserve more
than that!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And you?! What are you
all waiting for, huh?!
- [CLAMORING]
- [OBJECTS CLATTER]
[THUD]
Gabo.
What's your plan now?
You guys go home.
Okay, Gabo.
We'll take it from here.
- Let's go.
- Come on. Let's go home.
- Clean up here, okay?
- Yeah.
- We got this.
- Take care.
Alright! Let's start cleaning!
You know what to do.
They left us in charge here.
- There's money everywhere!
- Let's pick them up!
- There's more over there!
- Look at all those coins!
- [LIGHT FOOTSTEPS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
- Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning.
Your mom wants you to join
her for breakfast.
- Have you called Max?
- I knocked at her room earlier.
But there was no answer.
She's probably still asleep.
Okay, you go ahead.
- I'll follow in a bit. Thanks.
- Okay, ma'am.
[LIGHT FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[SAM] Max?
Max?
Let's have breakfast together.
I know that we have lots
of problems at work.
It can sometimes get toxic,
and there are times we bring
our stress at home.
But I hope that we won't
let it affect us.
We agreed that we'll have
each other's back, right?
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll go downstairs now, okay?
I'll see you there.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ISOBEL] Oh, hon!
Good morning!
Breakfast is ready.
I cooked it myself.
I'll just have some coffee.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, Sam!
Come, dear.
Let's have breakfast.
Come on.
Here. Okay.
Just please. Sit down.
Perfect!
Tell me if you want
anything else, okay?
I'll cook it for you.
I don't want anything else.
Thank you.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIGHS LOUDLY]
[ISOBEL] Oh!
Max, sit down.
I'm not hungry, Ma.
No, I insist!
It's been so long since this
family's been complete
on this table.
- Sorry, Ma. I'm just busy.
- No! Sit down!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you can't use your mouths
to eat the food in front of you,
why don't you use them
to finally talk?
[FRUSTRATED SIGH]
Can't anyone appreciate
what I'm doing here?!
- Thank you for breakfast.
No, I'm not talking
about the food!
I'm talking about us!
Can't we go back
to being a family
who gathers around
the dining table
to talk and enjoy the food?!
Don't blame yourself if we
can't be complete anymore...
...in the same way
that I don't blame you
for hoping that
could still happen again.
[ISOBEL] Ricardo, I'm not
blaming myself
because I know
I'm doing enough
for my family.
We may not be complete.
But we are still a family.
But sometimes, I wonder...
Can we still consider this
a family
with the way
we treat each other?
I keep trying to
fix things among you.
I keep trying
to prevent you from fighting.
Because all I want
is for us to be a normal family.
And I am not asking you
to appreciate me!
I just want you to show
some care for each other!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
My god...
I give up!
Suit yourselves!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, Gabo? Did you manage
to secure some money?
Will you just wait
until your father flatlines
before you do something?!
Do I have to do
everything again?!
I almost sold my body
to find us some cash!
Are you really just going to
sit there and do nothing?
You're going to leave this
on me again?!
Don't worry.
I'll find a way so Papa
can have his operation.
I promise I'll find a job.
All you do is make
promises you can't keep!
That's enough!
Betchay, could you please
go easy on Gabo?
The kid's doing his best!
He already promised--
I don't need promises!
What I need is money!
I'm begging you, Gabo!
We need money! Money!
And you think yelling at him
is going to help us?!
- Oh god.
- We should use this time...
...to think of how we
can afford Rudy's operation
and save him!
My goodness, Gabo!
[DISAPPOINTED SIGH]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VIA] Good morning, Sam!
- Good morning.
- Oh!
Will you request
for a CCTV footage too?
Of what?
Of Chinatown.
Ma'am Pia asked for a copy.
- Is that so?
- She talked to us
one by one last night.
She asked us about the mission.
- What did you tell her?
- The truth.
That if only Sir Seb hadn't
messed things up,
our mission would have
gone smoothly.
But no! He still fought
with that man.
Wait.
Who is that guy?
Was he the one who kissed you?
The truth is...
I don't know him.
One thing's for sure,
I'd love to meet him
so I can finally catch him.
He's pissing me off so bad.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Team leader!
Why are you here?
I've been staying up all night
reviewing your mission.
Good luck.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Sir?
Yes?
This is the report on
what happened in Chinatown.
Are you sure about this report?
Yes. It's impartial.
That's based off of happened
and what the agents have said.
"Agent Tuazon's performance
throughout the operation
that led to the arrest
of Victor Zafra was exemplary
and reflected the highest
standard expected of NCIA
personnel."
Is he that good?
Hmm... well...
Based on my investigation,
Sebastian was the one
who carried out the mission.
Sam just took the credit.
Took credit?
Sir, please read the report.
The truth won't deceive you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We've been going
around in circles.
I think we should ask around.
No. It's just straight ahead.
Estrella, stay here.
They might change their minds
when they see you.
Stay here and wait for me.
Hello!
Can I ask a few questions?
Do you know where
Rudy Magtibay lives?
The one who got shot
during the demolition?
Why? What do you need from them?
We'll only provide assistance.
[MAN] They live there.
- Here?
- [MAN] Yes, that's it.
Oh, right here! Thank you.
Hello, is anyone there?
- Hello!
- Who are you?
[MAX] Is this where
Rudy Magtibay lives?
The one who got shot
during the demolition?
- Yes, I'm his sister.
- [BETCHAY] I'm his wife.
Oh, hello!
- [BETCHAY] Hello.
- [GABO] Who are you?
Ah, this is Gabo,
Rudy's son.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAX] Ah...
I'm here to give financial aid.
To Rudy.
You're here to help?
Why? What organization
do you work for?
From...
from NGO!
We usually provide help
to those in need.
- I know that! Come inside!
- [MAX] Oh, alright!
- Come in.
- Wait a minute.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
You don't look like you work
for NGO.
If you came here
to settle this,
you're making a mistake.
Because we won't.
I'll make the one
who shot my father pay.
I work for NGO.
I'm here to give
Rudy's financial aid
to help his hospitalization.
This could really help him.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is a lot.
I'm sorry.
[ENVELOPE THUDS]
Hey, stop.
We could really use that money!
Stop meddling!
- Why not?
- Miss.
If you came here to buy us off,
you're mistaken.
You can't pay off
my fathers hospitalization!
And I'll make sure, that whoever
did that to my father,
will rot in jail!
We won't talk to you,
especially if you're a cop!
You're stepping out of line!
My brother's life is in danger,
and you have the nerve
to do this to us!
You should leave.
You might get involved in this.
Before I lose
my temper with you.
Leave!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAMENG] Gabo.
Gabo!
Please, just understand
that woman.
Maybe she just really
wants to help us.
Why, Auntie?
Just what do they think?
That just because we're poor
we can sell our dignity
so easily?
No!
Whoever shot Father
will definitely be imprisoned!
Even if it takes your father's
life in exchange?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLATTERS]
[RATTLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
So, Attorney, can I go now?
Victor, we're doing everything
we can to get you out--
If you're doing
everything you can,
I would've been
out of here already!
But where am I right now?
[VICTOR] Where? Am I free?
Tell me!
We have to go through
a lot of process--
That's because you're weak!
You're weak.
My family should've gotten me
a better lawyer.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Get me out of here
as soon as possible.
Yes, uh, of course!
And look for the man
who the group fought with.
Because it's his fault
that I'm here right now.
I'll make sure he pays
for everything he did myself.
[GRIM MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
They said that I violated
a lot of rules.
And that I'm not a good leader.
I could even get suspended.
Congratulations!
You did a great job.
There's no celebration.
Especially if there's a threat
of suspension.
Threat of suspension?!
Ihman is coming today
to take the motorcycle!
- He's taking it back!
- I'll call the police on you!
You utterly failed!
It was about to be sold!
So your father could finally get
an operation!
We almost had it!
Find the woman
who kidnapped Victor.
Tell me who that man is.
Investigate it yourself.
You're good right?
He'll pay for what he did
to Victor.
I really need to find that man.
How are we gonna start
tracking that guy down?
The motorcycle.
It will lead the way
for me to find him.
We need to get
the motorcycle back immediately.
[THUDS]
We'll get caught here
if we're not cautious!
We need to find
Gabo's motorcycle!
I believe
that guy is the key
for us to solve
this gold smuggling case.
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [MAN GRUNTING]
Let's search the whole place.
I need to get
the motorcycle back.
[ENGINE REVVING]